{"results":[{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,18000","2/3,6000"],"answer":"3","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"3","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":4786},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","2/3,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.5","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":7953},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,20000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"2","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":650},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,5000","3/2,15000"],"answer":"0.33","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":408},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","1/1,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":139},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","1/1,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":292},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":340},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","3/2,15000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":694},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,15000","1/1,5000"],"answer":"3","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":635},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":668},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","2/3,5000"],"answer":"3","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":701},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":642},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,15000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":699},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","1/1,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":629},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,6000","2/3,18000"],"answer":"0.33","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":775},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","1/1,20000"],"answer":"2","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":718},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":679},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"whichRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,10000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,whichRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,whichRectangle2","time":615}]}